Renaissance architecture photograph collection (Holland-Yugoslavia and Latin America)
Yale University Arts Library
- Architecture: Renaissance III. (Box 49)
  - Italy., 3804 (Box 49)
    - Individual locations., 3628 (Box 51)
      - Siena., 165 (Box 93)
        - Miscellaneous buildings, details and maps., 6 (Box 93)
        - Accademia di Belle Arte., 3 (Box 93)
        - Churches., 130 (Box 93)
          - Miscellaneous churches., 6 (Box 93)
          - Santa Caterina., 4 (Box 93)
          - Cathedral., 111 (Box 93)
            - Exterior., 1 (Box 93)
            - Interior., 10 (Box 93)
            - Pavement., 87 (Box 93)
              - Miscellaneous subjects., 20 (Box 94)
              - Allegorical figures., 5 (Box 94)
              - David., 4 (Box 94)
              - Death of Absalom., 4 (Box 94)
              - Emperor Sigismund., 2 (Box 94)
              - Funeral slab of Carlo Bartoli., 2 (Box 94)
              - The Story of Jephthah., 3 (Box 94)
              - Judith Freeing Betulia., 3 (Box 94)
              - Massacre of the Innocents., 8 (Box 94)
              - Moses., 9 (Box 94)
              - Pilgrimage of the Jews., 6 (Box 94)
              - Pursuit of Herod., 5 (Box 94)
              - Abraham Sacrificing Isaac., 2 (Box 94)
              - Seven Ages of Man., 3 (Box 94)
              - Sibyls., 11 (Box 95)
            - Libreria Piccolomini., 13 (Box 95)
          - San Domenico., 1 (Box 95)
          - Chiesa di Fontegiusta., 6 (Box 95)
          - San Martino., 2 (Box 95)
        - Loggia., 9 (Box 95)
          - Loggia dei Mercanti (Loggia di San Paolo)., 9 (Box 95)
        - Palaces., 17 (Box 95)
          - Miscellaneous palazzi., 6 (Box 95)
          - Palazzo Bandini-Piccolomini., 7 (Box 95)
          - Palazzo Signoria., 4 (Box 95)
      - Spello., 5 (Box 95)
        - Santa Maria Maggiore., 5 (Box 95)
      - Spoleto., 3 (Box 95)
      - Stupinigi., 11 (Box 96)
      - Taormina, Sicily., 5 (Box 96)
      - Tivoli., 26 (Box 96)
      - Todi., 17 (Box 96)
        - Miscellaneous buildings and details., 4 (Box 96)
        - Cathedral., 7 (Box 96)
        - Santa Maria della Consolazione., 6 (Box 96)
      - Toscanella., 1 (Box 96)
      - Trebbio (near Florence)., 3 (Box 96)
      - Turin., 42 (Box 96)
        - Miscellaneous buildings., 7 (Box 96)
        - Churches., 26 (Box 96)
          - Miscellaneous churches., 6 (Box 97)
          - Cathedral., 9 (Box 97)
          - Corpus Domini., 2 (Box 97)
          - San Lorenzo., 5 (Box 97)
          - Superga., 4 (Box 97)
        - Palaces., 9 (Box 97)
      - Urbino., 35 (Box 97)
        - Palazzo Ducale., 35 (Box 97)
          - Exterior., 5 (Box 97)
          - Interior., 15 (Box 97)
          - Details., 15 (Box 97)
      - Vallerano., 1 (Box 98)
      - Venice., 425 (Box 98)
        - Miscellaneous views and buildings., 12 (Box 98)
        - Arsenal., 1 (Box 98)
        - Bridges., 13 (Box 98)
          - Miscellaneous bridges., 1 (Box 98)
          - Bridge of Sighs., 4 (Box 98)
          - Rialto Bridge., 8 (Box 98)
        - Canals., 15 (Box 98)
          - Miscellaneous canals., 5 (Box 98)
          - Grand Canal., 10 (Box 98)
        - Churches., 184 (Box 98)
          - Miscellaneous churches., 27 (Box 99)
          - Church of the Frari., 5 (Box 99)
          - Church of the Jesuits., 4 (Box 99)
          - Church of the Redeemer (Il Redentore)., 8 (Box 99)
          - Chiesa del Scalzi., 2 (Box 99)
          - San Francesco della Vigna., 3 (Box 99)
          - San Giobbe., 13 (Box 99)
          - San Giorgio dei Greci., 3 (Box 99)
          - San Giorgio Maggiore., 15 (Box 99)
          - Ss. Giovanni e Paolo., 2 (Box 99)
          - Santa Maria Formosa., 3 (Box 99)
          - Santa Maria del Giglio., 1 (Box 99)
          - Santa Maria dei Miracoli., 45 (Box 99)
            - Exterior., 6 (Box 100)
            - Interior., 7 (Box 100)
            - Sculptural details., 32 (Box 100)
          - Santa Maria della Salute., 11 (Box 100)
          - San Rocco., 1 (Box 100)
          - San Sebastiano., 3 (Box 100)
          - San Zaccaria., 7 (Box 100)
        - Government buildings., 3 (Box 100)
          - Miscellaneous buildings., 1 (Box 100)
          - Procuratie Nuove., 2 (Box 101)
        - Libraries., 12 (Box 101)
          - Library of San Marco (Sansovino)., 12 (Box 101)
        - Palaces., 120 (Box 101)
          - Miscellaneous palazzi., 21 (Box 101)
          - Palazzo Cornaro della Ca' Grande., 3 (Box 101)
          - Palazzo Corner della Regina., 1 (Box 101)
          - Palazzo Corner-Spinelli., 2 (Box 101)
          - Palazzo Dario and Palazzo Barbaro., 2 (Box 101)
          - Palazzo Ducale., 69 (Box 101)
            - Court., 28 (Box 102)
            - Interiors., 41 (Box 102)
              - Miscellaneous rooms and details., 13 (Box 102)
              - Chiesetta., 3 (Box 102)
              - Doge's bedroom., 4 (Box 102)
              - Antecollegio., 3 (Box 102)
              - Sala del Collegio., 4 (Box 102)
              - Scala d'Oro., 6 (Box 102)
              - Senate Hall., 8 (Box 102)
          - Palazzo Grimani., 3 (Box 102)
          - Palazzo Minelli., 2 (Box 102)
          - Palazzo Montecuccoli., 2 (Box 102)
          - Palazzo Papadopoli., 1 (Box 102)
          - Palazzo Pesaro., 3 (Box 102)
          - Palazzo Rezzonico., 5 (Box 102)
          - Palazzo Vendramini., 3 (Box 102)
          - Palazzo Widman., 3 (Box 103)
        - Schools., 51 (Box 103)
          - Miscellaneous schools., 1 (Box 103)
          - Accademia di Belle Arti., 10 (Box 103)
          - Scuola di San Giorgio e Trifone., 7 (Box 103)
          - Scuola di San Giovanni Evangelista., 14 (Box 103)
          - Scuola di San Marco., 12 (Box 103)
          - Scuola di San Rocco., 7 (Box 103)
        - Squares., 14 (Box 103)
          - Piazza di San Marco., 14 (Box 104)
      - Verona., 49 (Box 104)
        - Miscellaneous views and buildings., 6 (Box 104)
        - Porta Palio., 2 (Box 104)
        - Churches., 16 (Box 104)
          - Miscellaneous churches., 3 (Box 104)
          - San Anastasia., 4 (Box 104)
          - San Bernardino., 3 (Box 104)
          - Santa Maria in Organo., 6 (Box 104)
        - Palaces., 25 (Box 104)
          - Palazzo Bevilacqua., 5 (Box 104)
          - Palazzo Canossa., 3 (Box 104)
          - Palazzo del Consiglio., 10 (Box 104)
          - Palazzo della Gran Guardia Vecchia., 2 (Box 104)
          - Palazzo Maffei., 2 (Box 104)
          - Palazzo Pompei., 2 (Box 104)
          - Palazzo Portalupi., 1 (Box 105)
      - Vicenza., 82 (Box 105)
        - Miscellaneous maps, buildings and views., 7 (Box 105)
        - Loggia del Capitano., 4 (Box 105)
        - Monte Berico., 2 (Box 105)
        - Olympic Theater., 7 (Box 105)
        - Palaces., 45 (Box 105)
          - Miscellaneous palazzi., 12 (Box 105)
          - Palazzo Branzo., 2 (Box 105)
          - Palazzo Chiericati., 7 (Box 105)
          - Palazzo Iseppo da Porto (Palazzo Festa)., 5 (Box 105)
          - Palazzo della Ragione., 6 (Box 105)
          - Palazzo Thienne-Bonin., 7 (Box 105)
          - Palazzo Valmarano., 6 (Box 106)
        - Villas., 17 (Box 106)
          - Miscellaneous villas., 2 (Box 106)
          - Villa Rotonda (Villa Capra)., 15 (Box 106)
      - Viterbo., 17 (Box 107)
  - Latvia., 1 (Box 107)
    - Miscellaneous locations., 1 (Box 107)
      - Riga., 1 (Box 107)
  - Poland., 15 (Box 107)
    - Individual locations., 15 (Box 107)
      - Cracow., 6 (Box 107)
      - Gdansk., 2 (Box 107)
      - Warsaw., 7 (Box 107)
  - Portugal., 42 (Box 107)
    - Miscellaneous locations., 13 (Box 107)
      - Guimaraes., 1 (Box 107)
      - Lomego., 2 (Box 107)
      - Lumiar., 1 (Box 107)
      - Oeiras., 3 (Box 107)
      - Olivenca., 1 (Box 107)
      - Viana do Castelo., 1 (Box 107)
      - Vila do Conde., 1 (Box 107)
      - Vila Real., 2 (Box 107)
      - Viseu., 1 (Box 107)
    - Individual locations., 29 (Box 107)
      - Belem., 4 (Box 107)
      - Braga., 4 (Box 107)
      - Lisbon., 4 (Box 107)
      - Mafra., 3 (Box 107)
      - Oporto., 8 (Box 107)
      - Queluz., 6 (Box 107)
  - Russia., 97 (Box 107)
    - Miscellaneous locations., 6 (Box 95)
      - Kiev., 2 (Box 95)
      - Ostankino., 2 (Box 95)
      - Zagorsk., 2 (Box 95)
    - Individual locations., 91 (Box 95)
      - Leningrad (Saint Petersburg)., 28 (Box 95)
        Includes a folio of prints of watercolors by V. Sadovnikova.
        - Miscellaneous buildings and views., 7 (Box 108)
        - Hermitage., 12 (Box 108)
        - Churches., 6 (Box 108)
        - Palaces., 3 (Box 108)
      - Moscow., 39 (Box 108)
        - Miscellaneous buildings., 1 (Box 108)
        - Kremlin., 16 (Box 108)
          - Miscellaneous buildings and views., 12 (Box 108)
          - Terem's Palace., 4 (Box 108)
        - Churches., 19 (Box 108)
          - Miscellaneous churches., 6 (Box 108)
          - Archangel Michael., 2 (Box 108)
          - Saint Basil Cathedral., 8 (Box 108)
          - Cathedral of the Assumption., 3 (Box 108)
        - Gates., 3 (Box 108)
      - Novodevichy., 2 (Box 108)
      - Pavlosk., 4 (Box 108)
      - Peterhof., 6 (Box 109)
      - Tsarskoe-Selo., 5 (Box 109)
      - Tsaritsyno., 7 (Box 109)
  - Spain., 454 (Box 109)
    - Architectural ornament., 5 (Box 109)
    - Miscellaneous locations., 25 (Box 109)
      - Alcaraz, Albacete., 1 (Box 109)
      - Almansa, Albacete., 1 (Box 109)
      - Arenys de Mar., 1 (Box 109)
      - Astorga., 1 (Box 109)
      - Azpeitia., 1 (Box 109)
      - Baeza, Jaen., 1 (Box 109)
      - Calahorra, Granada., 3 (Box 109)
      - El Carpio., 1 (Box 109)
      - Gijon, Asturias., 1 (Box 109)
      - Guadalupe., 1 (Box 109)
      - Guadix, Granada., 1 (Box 109)
      - Hernani., 1 (Box 109)
      - Jerez de la Frontera, Cadiz., 1 (Box 109)
      - Leon., 1 (Box 109)
      - Lerida., 1 (Box 109)
      - Lerma., 1 (Box 109)
      - Lupiana, Guadelajara., 1 (Box 109)
      - Nuevo Baztan., 1 (Box 109)
      - Santa Maria del Campo, near Burgos., 1 (Box 109)
      - Ucles., 1 (Box 109)
      - Viana., 1 (Box 109)
      - Vich., 1 (Box 109)
      - Villagargia de Campos, Vallodolid., 1 (Box 109)
    - Individual locations., 424 (Box 109)
      - Alcala de Henares., 19 (Box 109)
        - Miscellaneous buildings., 6 (Box 109)
        - Archiepiscopal Palace (Archbishop's Palace)., 7 (Box 109)
        - University., 6 (Box 109)
      - Alicante., 3 (Box 110)
      - Antequera., 2 (Box 110)
      - Aranjuez., 5 (Box 110)
      - Avila., 7 (Box 110)
      - Barcelona., 1 (Box 110)
      - Burgos., 8 (Box 110)
        - Miscellaneous buildings., 5 (Box 110)
        - City Gate of Santa Maria., 3 (Box 110)
      - Cadiz., 2 (Box 110)
      - Chinchilla de Montearagon, Albacete., 2 (Box 110)
      - Cordova., 14 (Box 110)
      - Coria., 3 (Box 110)
      - Ecija, Seville., 3 (Box 111)
      - Escorial., 30 (Box 111)
        - Miscellaneous buildings and views., 17 (Box 111)
        - Church., 9 (Box 111)
        - Quarters of Phillip II., 4 (Box 111)
      - Escorial de Abajo., 3 (Box 111)
      - La Granja., 5 (Box 111)
      - Granada., 35 (Box 111)
        - Miscellaneous buildings., 2 (Box 111)
        - Palace of Charles V., 10 (Box 111)
        - Churches., 23 (Box 111)
          - Miscellaneous churches., 17 (Box 112)
          - Cathedral., 6 (Box 112)
      - Guadalajara., 6 (Box 112)
      - Haro, Logrono., 2 (Box 112)
      - Jaen., 4 (Box 112)
      - Jerez., 4 (Box 112)
      - Leon., 13 (Box 112)
      - Loyola., 1 (Box 112)
      - Madrid., 23 (Box 112)
        - Miscellaneous buildings and views., 9 (Box 112)
        - Churches., 14 (Box 112)
          - Miscellaneous churches., 7 (Box 112)
          - Church of the Benedictines of Montserrat., 7 (Box 113)
      - Malaga., 3 (Box 113)
      - Medina del Campo, Vallodolid., 5 (Box 113)
      - Montserrat., 1 (Box 113)
      - Mues (San Gregorio Ostiense)., 2 (Box 113)
      - Murcia., 9 (Box 113)
      - Nuevo Baztan., 6 (Box 113)
      - Osuna., 3 (Box 113)
      - Palma de Mallorca., 10 (Box 113)
      - Penaranda de Duero, Burgos., 2 (Box 113)
      - Pontevedra., 2 (Box 113)
      - Plasencia., 4 (Box 113)
      - Ronda., 3 (Box 113)
      - Salamanca., 34 (Box 113)
        - Miscellaneous buildings and views., 19 (Box 114)
        - Patio of Escuelas Menores., 5 (Box 114)
        - Houses., 10 (Box 114)
          - Miscellaneous houses., 5 (Box 114)
          - House of the Shells., 5 (Box 114)
      - Santiago de Compostela., 15 (Box 114)
      - Saragossa., 17 (Box 114)
      - Segovia., 2 (Box 114)
      - Seville., 35 (Box 114)
        - Miscellaneous buildings and views., 11 (Box 114)
        - Government buildings., 11 (Box 114)
          - Ayuntamento (town hall)., 11 (Box 115)
        - Hospitals., 4 (Box 115)
        - Palaces., 9 (Box 115)
          - Miscellaneous palaces., 3 (Box 115)
          - Alcazar., 6 (Box 115)
      - Siguenza, Guadalajara., 5 (Box 115)
      - Sobrado de los Monjes., 4 (Box 115)
      - Tarragona., 2 (Box 115)
      - Toledo., 44 (Box 115)
        - Miscellaneous buildings and views., 6 (Box 115)
        - Bridge of l'Alcantara., 6 (Box 115)
        - Churches., 12 (Box 115)
          - Miscellaneous churches., 3 (Box 115)
          - Cathedral., 9 (Box 115)
        - Government buildings., 2 (Box 115)
          - Ayuntamento (town hall)., 2 (Box 115)
        - Hospitals., 18 (Box 115)
          - Miscellaneous hospitals., 6 (Box 115)
          - Hospital of Santa Cruz., 12 (Box 116)
      - Trujillo, Caceres., 4 (Box 116)
      - Ubeda, Jaen., 4 (Box 116)
      - Valencia., 4 (Box 116)
      - Vallodolid., 9 (Box 116)
        - Miscellaneous buildings., 8 (Box 116)
        - University., 1 (Box 116)
  - Sweden., 25 (Box 116)
    - Individual locations., 25 (Box 116)
      - Drottningholm., 9 (Box 116)
      - Gripsholm., 2 (Box 116)
      - Kalmar., 2 (Box 116)
      - Stockholm., 9 (Box 116)
      - Trondheim., 2 (Box 116)
      - Vadstena., 1 (Box 116)
  - Switzerland., 17 (Box 116)
    - Miscellaneous locations., 4 (Box 116)
      - Ferney, Geneva., 1 (Box 116)
      - Geneva., 1 (Box 116)
      - Interlachen (near)., 1 (Box 116)
      - Rheinau., 1 (Box 116)
    - Individual locations., 13 (Box 116)
      - Berne., 3 (Box 116)
      - Einsiedeln., 5 (Box 116)
      - Saint Gallen., 1 (Box 116)
      - Zurich., 4 (Box 116)
  - Yugoslavia., 10 (Box 116)
    - Individual locations., 10 (Box 116)
      - Dubrovnik (Ragusa)., 6 (Box 116)
      - Sibenik (Sebenico)., 4 (Box 117)
  - Latin America., 1192 (Box 117)
    - Bolivia., 27 (Box 117)
      - Miscellaneous locations., 8 (Box 117)
        - Catavi., 1 (Box 117)
        - Cliza., 1 (Box 117)
        - Cochambamba., 1 (Box 117)
        - Copacabana., 1 (Box 117)
        - Laja., 1 (Box 117)
        - Monte Sajama, (near)., 1 (Box 117)
        - Sucre., 1 (Box 117)
        - Tiahuanaco., 1 (Box 117)
      - Individual locations., 19 (Box 117)
        - La Paz., 4 (Box 117)
        - Potosi., 12 (Box 117)
        - Sicasica., 3 (Box 117)
    - Brazil., 43 (Box 117)
      - Miscellaneous locations., 4 (Box 117)
        - Sao Goncaluo, near Niteroi., 2 (Box 117)
        - S. Pedro de Mariana., 1 (Box 117)
        - S. Salvado., 1 (Box 117)
      - Individual locations., 39 (Box 117)
        - Congonhas do Campo., 2 (Box 117)
        - Olinda, Pernambuco., 4 (Box 117)
        - Ouro Preto., 18 (Box 117)
          - Miscellaneous buildings., 7 (Box 117)
          - Igreja do Carmo., 6 (Box 117)
          - Sao Francisco., 5 (Box 117)
        - Recife., 4 (Box 118)
        - Rio de Janeiro., 1 (Box 118)
        - Salvador (formerly Bahia)., 8 (Box 118)
        - Sao Salvador., 2 (Box 118)
    - Colombia., 58 (Box 118)
      - Miscellaneous locations., 2 (Box 118)
        - Mompos., 1 (Box 118)
        - Quito., 1 (Box 118)
      - Individual locations., 56 (Box 118)
        - Bogota., 19 (Box 118)
          - Miscellaneous buildings and details., 7 (Box 118)
          - Cathedral., 3 (Box 118)
          - San Francisco Church., 9 (Box 118)
        - Cali., 2 (Box 118)
        - Cartagena., 13 (Box 118)
        - Manizales., 1 (Box 118)
        - Maraquita., 2 (Box 118)
        - Medellin., 1 (Box 118)
        - Mongui., 3 (Box 118)
        - Popayan., 4 (Box 118)
        - Santa Marta., 1 (Box 118)
        - Tunja., 10 (Box 119)
    - Cuba., 4 (Box 119)
      - Individual locations., 4 (Box 119)
        - Havana., 3 (Box 119)
        - Santiago de Cuba., 1 (Box 119)
    - Dominican Republic., 18 (Box 119)
      - Individual locations., 18 (Box 119)
        - Santo Domingo., 18 (Box 119)
    - Ecuador., 17 (Box 119)
      - Individual locations., 17 (Box 119)
        - Quito., 17 (Box 119)
    - Guatemala., 190 (Box 119)
      - Miscellaneous locations., 3 (Box 119)
        - Unknown., 2 (Box 119)
        - Totonicapan., 1 (Box 119)
      - Individual locations., 187 (Box 119)
        - Antigua., 179 (Box 119)
          - Architectural ornament., 1 (Box 119)
          - Cuidad Vieja., 178 (Box 119)
            - Miscellaneous buildings., 3 (Box 119)
            - Bridges., 2 (Box 119)
            - Churches., 130 (Box 119)
              - Miscellaneous churches., 5 (Box 119)
              - Belen., 2 (Box 119)
              - Calvario., 5 (Box 119)
              - Candelaria., 4 (Box 120)
              - Capuchinas., 10 (Box 120)
              - Carmen., 4 (Box 120)
              - Cathedral., 8 (Box 120)
              - La Compania., 3 (Box 120)
              - Concepcion., 5 (Box 120)
              - Escuela de Cristo., 5 (Box 120)
              - Guadalupe., 3 (Box 120)
              - Hermanos de San Juan., 3 (Box 120)
              - Jocotenango., 5 (Box 120)
              - La Merced., 12 (Box 120)
              - Recoleccion., 3 (Box 120)
              - Remedios., 3 (Box 121)
              - San Agustin., 3 (Box 121)
              - Santa Ana., 2 (Box 121)
              - Santa Catalina., 2 (Box 121)
              - Santa Clara., 6 (Box 121)
              - San Cristobal., 2 (Box 121)
              - Santa Cruz., 4 (Box 121)
              - San Francisco., 9 (Box 121)
              - Santa Isabel., 4 (Box 121)
              - San Jeronimo., 2 (Box 121)
              - San Jose., 4 (Box 121)
              - Santa Rosa., 7 (Box 121)
              - Santa Teresa., 5 (Box 121)
            - Fountains., 5 (Box 121)
            - Government buildings., 1 (Box 122)
            - Houses., 17 (Box 122)
            - Palaces., 5 (Box 122)
              - Episcopal Palace., 5 (Box 122)
            - Schools., 15 (Box 122)
              - Seminario Tridentino., 8 (Box 122)
              - Universidad., 7 (Box 122)
          - Guatemala City., 6 (Box 122)
          - Xilotepeque, Jalapa., 2 (Box 122)
    - Honduras., 5 (Box 122)
      - Unknown location., 1 (Box 122)
      - Miscellaneous locations., 4 (Box 122)
        - Choluteca., 1 (Box 122)
        - Omoa., 1 (Box 122)
        - Tegucigalpa., 1 (Box 123)
    - Mexico., 444 (Box 123)
      - Architectural ornament., 3 (Box 123)
      - Miscellaneous locations., 58 (Box 123)
        - Acambaro., 1 (Box 123)
        - Acatepec., 1 (Box 123)
        - Amecameca., 2 (Box 123)
        - Angahua., 2 (Box 123)
        - Atlixco., 1 (Box 123)
        - Atotonilco el Grande., 3 (Box 123)
        - Calpan., 1 (Box 123)
        - Campeche., 2 (Box 123)
        - Chimalhuacan Chalco., 1 (Box 123)
        - Coyoacan., 1 (Box 123)
        - Cuilapan de Guerrero., 3 (Box 123)
        - Cuitzeo., 3 (Box 123)
        - Durango., 1 (Box 123)
        - Dzemul., 2 (Box 123)
        - Erongaricuaro., 1 (Box 123)
        - Huejotzingo., 3 (Box 123)
        - Ixmiquilpan., 1 (Box 123)
        - Izamal., 1 (Box 123)
        - Lagos de Moreno., 1 (Box 123)
        - Los Remedior., 1 (Box 123)
        - Malinalco (?)., 1 (Box 123)
        - Monterey., 2 (Box 123)
        - Morelia., 2 (Box 123)
        - Patzcuaro., 2 (Box 123)
        - Saltillo., 1 (Box 123)
        - San Angel., 2 (Box 123)
        - Sinaxtla, Oaxaca., 1 (Box 123)
        - Tecali., 2 (Box 123)
        - Tentenanco, Valley of., 1 (Box 123)
        - Tepeapulco., 1 (Box 123)
        - Texupa., 1 (Box 123)
        - Tlahuelilpan., 1 (Box 123)
        - Tlalpan., 2 (Box 123)
        - Tlaquiltenango., 1 (Box 123)
        - Tula., 1 (Box 123)
        - Tzintzuntzan., 2 (Box 123)
        - Uruapan., 1 (Box 123)
        - Zimapan., 1 (Box 123)
        - Zinacautepec., 1 (Box 123)
      - Individual locations., 383 (Box 123)
        - Acolman., 10 (Box 123)
        - Actopan., 4 (Box 124)
        - Charo., 4 (Box 124)
        - Cholula., 6 (Box 124)
        - Cuernavaca., 5 (Box 124)
        - Guadalajara., 4 (Box 124)
        - Guadalupe., 4 (Box 124)
        - Guanajuato., 15 (Box 124)
        - Merida., 3 (Box 124)
        - Mexico City., 139 (Box 124)
          - Miscellaneous buildings and monuments., 11 (Box 124)
          - Maps and plans., 5 (Box 125)
          - Churches., 76 (Box 125)
            - Miscellaneous churches., 41 (Box 125)
            - Cathedral., 35 (Box 125)
          - Government buildings., 8 (Box 126)
          - Houses., 15 (Box 126)
          - Schools., 24 (Box 126)
            - Miscellaneous schools., 3 (Box 126)
            - Las Vizcainas., 21 (Box 126)
        - Oaxaca., 9 (Box 126)
        - Puebla., 16 (Box 126)
        - Queretaro., 31 (Box 126)
          - Miscellaneous buildings., 6 (Box 127)
          - Santa Clara., 15 (Box 127)
          - Santa Rosa., 10 (Box 127)
        - Salamanca., 16 (Box 127)
        - San Luis de Potosi., 4 (Box 127)
        - San Miguel Allende., 4 (Box 127)
        - Taxco., 7 (Box 127)
        - Tepeaca., 4 (Box 127)
        - Teposcolula., 6 (Box 128)
        - Tepozotlan., 17 (Box 128)
        - Tepoztlan., 8 (Box 128)
        - Tlalmanalco., 5 (Box 128)
        - Tlatelolco., 3 (Box 128)
        - Tlaxcala., 10 (Box 128)
        - Tonantzintla., 5 (Box 128)
        - Xochimilco., 8 (Box 128)
        - Yanhuitlan., 3 (Box 128)
        - Yecapixtla., 3 (Box 128)
        - Yurira., 19 (Box 129)
        - Zacatecas., 11 (Box 129)
    - Panama., 13 (Box 129)
      - Miscellaneous locations., 7 (Box 129)
        - Alanje., 1 (Box 129)
        - Panama City., 2 (Box 129)
        - Parita., 1 (Box 129)
        - Porto Bello., 1 (Box 129)
        - Santiago., 1 (Box 129)
        - Taboga., 1 (Box 129)
      - Individual locations., 6 (Box 129)
        - Old Panama., 6 (Box 129)
    - Peru., 364 (Box 129)
      - Miscellaneous locations., 9 (Box 129)
        - Acora., 1 (Box 129)
        - Andahuaylillas., 1 (Box 129)
        - Ayabihi (?)., 1 (Box 129)
        - Capacabania., 1 (Box 129)
        - Cerro de Pasco., 1 (Box 129)
        - Huancayo., 1 (Box 129)
        - Ollantaitambo., 1 (Box 129)
        - Pisco., 1 (Box 129)
        - Urubamba., 1 (Box 129)
      - Individual locations., 355 (Box 129)
        - Arequipa., 19 (Box 129)
          - Miscellaneous buildings., 11 (Box 129)
          - La Compania., 3 (Box 129)
          - Cathedral., 5 (Box 129)
        - Ayacucho., 38 (Box 129)
          - Miscellaneous buildings., 5 (Box 129)
          - Cathedral., 8 (Box 129)
          - La Compania., 4 (Box 130)
          - Santa Ana., 3 (Box 130)
          - Santa Clara., 2 (Box 130)
          - Santo Domingo., 7 (Box 130)
          - San Francisco de Asis., 1 (Box 130)
          - San Juan de Dios., 2 (Box 130)
          - Santa Teresa., 6 (Box 130)
        - Cajamarca., 26 (Box 130)
          - Miscellaneous buildings., 5 (Box 130)
          - El Belen., 8 (Box 130)
          - Cathedral., 5 (Box 130)
          - La Recoleta., 3 (Box 130)
          - San Francisco., 5 (Box 130)
        - Checcacupe (near Cuzco)., 3 (Box 130)
        - Cuzco., 55 (Box 130)
          - Miscellaneous buildings and views., 8 (Box 130)
          - Churches., 42 (Box 130)
            - Miscellaneous churches., 4 (Box 131)